原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     千只鹤飞过波千鸟  tong大梨
翻译     AlgerDestiny  五天  二糯米
翻译     A序列  马丁马丁回音山  建国  秀英
校对     屯栗子
时间轴     Caroline
后期     渔夫
总监     屯栗子
辛普森一家
第三十一季  第十五集
只有我记得今天开始夏令时了吗
Am I the only one who remembered daylight savings time?
推销杀人犯
杀人城
你有权保持沉默
证据
严禁触碰
威斯康星州
"给我定罪"州
网飞股票
最有可能的杀人犯
已经在这里呆了十七年
Been here 17 years.
上过HBO  网飞和一集"猎房"国际版
Been on the HBO, the Netflix and one House Hunters International.
出售
多伦多
不过现在有两个新的强悍律师帮我
But now I got two new hotshot lawyers working my case.
那间小屋里没有挣扎
No sign of a struggle,
或DNA痕迹
no DNA evidence in the cabin
也没有漂亮的年轻女人失踪
and no attractive young woman declared missing.
我觉得很有可能没有人被谋杀
I think there's a very real chance no one was murdered.
我就在给他定罪的陪审团里
I was on the jury that convicted him.
要知道其实没有受害者的话
Had we known there was no victim,
我们可能就不会投票有罪了
we might not have voted guilty.
我重复  可能就不会
I repeat, might not.
重磅好消息
Fantastic news.
我们喜获第二季续订
We got picked up for a second season.
那我的案子[吸引力]呢
And my appeal?
大部分25到54岁的女性
Mostly to women 25 to 54.
哦你是说上诉的案子啊
Oh. You mean "appeal" appeal.
那是没戏了
Oh, well, that's not happening.
怎么了宝贝
What is it, sweetie?
要打嗝吗[发表意见]
Are you gassy?
她什么时候不想  宝宝打嗝
Uh, when is she not gassy? Baby burp.
你要是会说话就好了
If only you could talk.
就是那些说不了话的人才会有很多想要分享的
It's the people who can't speak that have so much to share.
也可能不是这样
Or maybe not.
等一下  我记得有个节目
Wait a minute. I think there's a show
教宝宝手势语言
about teaching a baby sign language.
宝宝手势
还要
牛奶
妈妈
我终于可以跟宝宝说话了
I could finally talk to my baby.
阿麦  我们这周都可以快乐地反复练习
Maggie, we have a fun week of repetitive drills ahead.
我想知道这孩子到底生什么气
I wonder what the kid was so upset about.
别担心  小宝宝  我撑到早上没问题
Don't worry, little baby. I'll be okay till morning.
现在我完了
Now I'm screwed.
恭喜你们  宝宝们
Congratulations, babies,
急救
我们今天学了一些很棒的手势
we've learned some great signs today.
担心永远不嫌早
希望你们不会"还要"因为我们已经"完了"
I hope you don't want "more," because we're "all done,"
因为我们的政府资助已经
because our government funding
"没有了"
"ran out."
阿麦  你是"还要"还是"完了"
Okay, Maggie. Do you want "more" or are you "all done"?
"再来点"还是"够了"
"More" or "all done"?
太好了  现在燕麦圈吃完了
Great, now I am out Cheerios.
我还以为是离得远所以看着小的甜甜圈呢
Oh, I thought they were doughnuts that were really far away.
还要吗  还要吗
More? More?
22点了  你炸了
Oh, that's 22, you are busted.
17点一定要说"够了"
Always say "all done" on a hard seventeen.
你会说吗
Can you say that?
17点
Hard seventeen.
别教她赌博
Don't teach her gambling.
开始吧  荷官  再来一局
Let's go dealer, one more hand.
先生  我不想挣你的钱
Sir, I don't want to take your money.
半月
一定要确保你杀的勇士真的死了
Remember to make sure the warriors you kill are actually dead.
我建议用刀刺
I recommand stabbing,
泼硫酸
dissolving in acid,
屁股上绑炸药
dynamite in the butt.
杰森  你的晚餐要来不及了
Jason, you are late for dinner.
妈妈  我在对着三千万人说话呢
Mom, I am talking to 30 millions peolple.
煮死
Boil them.
让猪把他们吃掉
let pigs eat them.
炸成肯德基
Kentucky Fry them.
别在阿麦面前玩这种游戏  她会做噩梦的
Don't play that infront of Maggie, she will have nightmares.
随你便
Suit yourself.
这个才像话
This is more like it.
汉瑟尔把浑身是血的女巫铲进烤箱
Hansel shoved the blood-covered witch into the oven.
"我要活活烧死了"  女巫尖叫道
"I am burning alive", screamed the witch.
还要  还要
More? More?
你还想要书
You want more book?
我的宝贝在和我交流
My baby is communicating with me.
我来检验一下
Let me test it out.
你喜欢豌豆吗
Do you like peas?
再来点
你喜欢苹果酱吗
Do you like applesauce?
再来点
你喜欢星战的电影吗
Do you like Star Wars movies.
够了
那尤达宝宝呢
What about Baby Yoda.
我曾经是美国人最爱的宝宝
这太让人激动了
This is so exciting.
快看  看看阿麦可以干什么
Look, look what Maggie can do.
阿麦  你还想再来点吗
Maggie, do you want more?
真是好姑娘
That's my girl.
大家快看啊  她做到了
Look everyone, she is doing it.
太好了
Yeah, that's great.
爸爸  看看这个
Dad, check this out.
他只在我们不看他的时候唱歌
He only sings when we're not looking.
经典的夸张幽默
Classic aggravation humor.
一只跳舞的青蛙
A dancing frog.
我猜它煮起来特别美味
Bet that would cook up nice.
就因为这些东西
You're missing a crucial moment in Maggie's development
你们错过了阿麦的成长
because of these.
从现在开始
From now on,
我们要限制看这些破手机的时间
we're gonna limit the time we spend looking at our stupid phones.
太好了
Yeah, that's great.
然后我们可以聊一聊了
And then we'll have a conversation.
史蒂夫·乔布斯不会让他的孩子用平板电脑
Steve Jobs wouldn't let his children use his iPads,
我想他也是一位优秀的家长
and he was a great parent, I assume.
从现在起  所有人每周只有半小时的观看时间
From now on, everyone gets a half hour of screen time a week.
一言为定
And that's it.
真的吗  马姬
Really, Marge?
你觉得你能放弃拼趣吗
You think you can give up your Pinterest?
我的失败蛋糕作品很重要
My cake fails are important.
有人做不成蛋糕  他们要知道自己不是一个人
If people fail at cake, they need to be told.
好吧  包括我在内所有人每周半小时的时间
Okay. Half an hour a week for everyone, including me.
我觉得你有什么东西忘记了
I believe there's something you're forgetting.
还有呢
And?
不要再看屏幕了  包括你
No more screens. You, too.
一周后
在这座中心里
Here at Messages,
我们用人道的方式解决你的屏幕瘾
we treat your addiction humanely,
屏幕网瘾矫正中心
辅以徒步  骑单车
with hiking and biking
还有人类和老鼠共通的事情上
and human equivalents of things that work with rats.
我们需要你死后的大脑
And all we ask for is your brain when you die.
但愿这个地方没有存在的必要
Well, let's pray this place won't be necessary.
好了  集合
All right, let's round 'em up.
已经过去了一周
Okay. It's been one week.
让我看看你们的屏幕使用时间
Let me check your screen times.
屏幕使用时间22分钟
屏幕使用时间17分钟
无屏幕使用时间
哇  时间好少
Wow. They're really low.
我真为你们骄傲
I'm so proud of you.
我都不记得折书脊这件事有多爽了
I forgot how great it was to crack the spine of a book.
《通往权力之路》
罗伯特·卡罗  著
我更冷静了  更幸福了
I'm calmer, I'm happier,
我见识到了从未见过的事情
I'm seeing things I never saw before.
你知道我们养的第二条狗是只猫吗
Did you know our second dog is a cat?
乔家里程数和屏幕使用时间撤销服务
抱歉  我上次落下了
Sorry, last time I was here,
撤销屏幕使用时间的扳手
I left my screen time reversal wrench.
我来拿回它
I could just get that back.
原来你们一直让他撤销屏幕使用时间
You guys have been having this man dial back your screen time?
看来我弄丢一家生意
Oops. Looks like I just lost a contract.
那么有人想买货车吗
Well, anybody want to buy a van?
只开过"两"公里哦
It only has two miles on it.
搞什
What the...?
闭上眼
Okay, close your eyes.
我要把它们放到你们永远找不到的地方
I'm putting these someplace you'll never find them.
1001音效
春田核电站
没手机玩  待在公司无所事事
No cell phone. Stuck at work all day with nothing to do.
《2002年核安全更新版》
紧急
闲到看我的脚
Lookin' at my feet.
老兄  无聊了吗
Hey, big guy. What, are you bored?
你要不玩玩报纸上的《每日一拼》
Why don't you do the Daily Jumble in the paper?
还原单词解开谜团
Unscramble the words to solve a funny riddle.
原来是这样
Oh, that's what it is.
我一直以为校对员中风了
I thought the proofreader had a stroke.
冷却液过热
让我瞅瞅
Let's see.
"D-D-A"
"D-D-A."
Hmm. "D-D-A."
"D-D-A"
"D-D-A." Hmm.
"爸爸"
"Dad."
是"爸爸"  我想出来了
"Dad." I got something!
人生第一次拼出了字谜
For the first time ever, I solved a puzzle.
拼字哈佛大学
你比我聪明
"爸爸把派全吃了"
"Dad ate all the pie."
快给报社打电话  说有人解出来了
Call the newspaper. Tell them someone has solved it.
另外给我拿个派
And get me some pie.
我喜欢自己不玩手机的状态
I love not using a phone.
跟世界更融合了
It's made me much more in tune with the world.
好像感官都变得灵敏
It's like my senses are heightened.
阿麦  该走了
Okay, Maggie, time to go.
跟姨姨们说再见
Say goodbye to your aunts.
身上有垃圾味的火怪
真可爱
So cute.
她在表达什么
What's she saying?
她在我们身边总是睡得这么香
She always sleeps so good when she's here.
小心  如果我们以过于陡峭的角度
Careful. If we enter the Martian atmosphere
进入火星大气层  会被烧死的
at too steep an angle, we'll burn up.
告诉我的家人我爱他们
Tell my family I love them.
他们知道的  斯蒂夫  他们知道
They know that, Steve. They know.
巴仔在用想象玩耍呢
Bart has to use his imagination.
这里是木星一号  收到吗
This is Jupiter One. Do you copy?
收到
I copy.
你在干啥
What are you doing?
和木星一号通信
I'm talking to Jupiter One.
让你见识见识真正的木星一号
Oh, I'll show you Jupiter One.
木星一号呼叫任务控制台
Jupiter One to mission control.
发射光子鱼雷
Firing photon torpedoes.
春田老图书馆
我在写一篇长达两页的重要论文
Um, I'm doing a very important two-page paper.
你们有办法
Do you have any way to find
不用电脑来找书吗
a book without using a computer?
老式的卡片目录在地下室里
Well, the old card catalogue is in the basement.
记得边走边敲  可以把负鼠吓跑
Bang on this pot to scare the possums away.
好吧
Okay.
复古卡片
Mmm, old card stock.
多么有形的存在
So tactile.
-现在可以吃她了吗
-别急  先继续扮演负鼠
看  这一张上还有手写的注解
Look, this one has an old handwritten note.
"亲爱的读者"  不就是我吗
"Dear Reader..." Ooh, that's me.
另请参阅《脱蜡技术指南》
"See also: Lost Wax Technique."
我会去参阅的
I will see also.
"NJXI"
"N-J-X-I."
倒霉
Jinx.
"PIUQ"  玩笑
"P-I-U-Q." Quip.
我能拼自己都不知道的词
I'm solving words I don't even know.
*混乱之舞  啦啦啦  啦啦啦*
*Jumble boogie, doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo*
*给老子爬  给老子爬*
*Get down, get down*
*不做笨蛋  啦啦啦  啦啦啦*
*With the goobie, doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo*
*所有难题  小菜一碟*
*Unjumbled that is boogie*
*啦啦啦  啦啦啦  我是解谜的小行家*
*Doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo, solve a jumble*
*世界给我小心点  哪怕我谦虚又宽容*
*In your face, world, I'm so humble*
*来转个圈圈*
*Now, watch me twirl.*
核反应堆芯
好了  接下来
Okay, okay.
我需要普坦纳丝卡意面酱的食谱
I need the recipe for puttanesca sauce.
不能上网查
Can't go online.
没问题  我有烹饪书
No problem. I've got cookbooks.
《帕德玛·拉克施密的热辣风味》
Padma Lakshmi's Hot and Zesty.
《蒂凡尼·哈迪斯的趣味萝卜厨房》
Tiffany Haddish's Fun with Radishes.
我做了14种  也没有那么有趣
I made 14 of those, they weren't that fun.
我知道该找谁了
I know who to call.
喂
Hello?
请问要怎么做普坦纳丝卡意面酱
What's the recipe for puttanesca sauce?
你想要食谱
Oh, you want-a the recipe?
没问题  去找支笔记下来
Sure, sure, get a pencil.
第一步  到店里来
Step-a one... you come here.
第二步  付钱
Step-a two... you pay for it.
第三步  我把你要的酱淋在意面上
Step-a three...I put it on-a some pasta.
就这么简单
And that's-a the recipe!
多么美好的一天啊
Oh, what a great day.
谁说不是呢
Oh, you said it.
我今天花了足足五分钟观察太阳
I spent five minutes today just looking at the sun.
妈妈去哪了
Hey, where's Mom?
为什么衣柜里有鼠标的声音
And why do I hear clicking from this closet?
意大利面
欧歌搜索  意大利面酱汁
等一下下
Hold on a beat. Just... hold on.
是谁说不能使用电子设备的
Who was the one who said no screen time?
谁说的
Who?
是你自己
It was you.
我知道
I know.
但我控制不住
I have a problem.
所以我在网瘾矫正中心
So, I'm signing us all up for a month
为我们报名了一个月的治疗
at that screen addiction rehab center.
但成瘾的不是我们  是你
But we're not addicted, you are!
成瘾的人都会说这句话
That's exactly what an addict would say.
正常人也会这么说
Or a normal person.
这句也是
That's also what an addict would say.
那成瘾的人不说什么话
Well, what wouldn't  an addict say?!
肯定不是你这句
Not that, that's for sure.
我们明天就出发
We'll all go there starting tomorrow.
那我来照顾宠物
And I'll watch the pets.
我领回来了好几只
I brought a bunch of them inside.
我是一只小幼狼
I'm the beta.
我们承诺  免费治疗您的第五次复发
我们到了吗
Are we there yet?
彻底清醒
治疗赌瘾或者赢双倍钱回家
我们到了吗
Are we there yet?
如名人死亡漩涡所见
为美国演员工会成员提供优惠
我们到了吗
Are we there yet?
-我们到了吗  -别吵了
- Are we there yet? - Knock off that racket!
我们到了吗
我说停下
I said knock it off!
屏幕网瘾矫正中心
明明是妈妈有网瘾
Mom's got the problem.
为什么我们也要被困在这...
How come we're stuck in...
天堂
paradise?
禅宗花园  无边泳池
Oh, Zen gardens, infinity pool?
随叫随到德鲁医生
Dr. Drew on call?
美国一档同名时事节目主持人
我来这里是因为我玩水果忍者上瘾了
I'm just here because I can't stop Fruit Ninja.
去死吧  芒果们
Die, mangoes, die!
如果矫正中心是这样  那我已经对这里上瘾了
If this is an addiction center, I'm hooked.
欢迎来到屏幕网瘾矫正中心
Welcome to Messages.
我是隆德医生
I am Dr. Lund.
医生  这监狱太赞了
Doc, this prison is great.
对我们一家再合适不过了
Nothing but the best for my family.
我只有一个问题
I just have one question.
在这里治疗要花多少钱
How much does this place cost?
你们的治疗费完全是由
Your stay is entirely funded by donations
心存愧疚的科技界亿万富翁捐款资助的
from tech billionaires, who feel guilty
因为是他们的颠覆性科技产品害你们上瘾的
that their sleek, disruptive technology put you here.
免费
It's free?
孩子们  我们找到今年的度假屋了
Kids, we've found our summer home.
成年人将进行更健康
The adults will reconnect with healthier,
更需要时间考验的日常活动
time-tested alternatives
比如吃饭 喝酒  婚外性行为
like eating, drinking, fornicating,
通奸  不停捉迷藏
fornicating, relentless hide and seek,
编辫子
the braiding of hair,
听达纳·古德的播客
listening to Dana Gould's podcast.
美国演员  曾为《辛普森一家》配音
四个人穿着《黑湖妖谭》的服装
Four people suffocated
1954年美国恐怖片
没能及时脱下
in the Creature from the Black Lagoon's suit
导致窒息而死
until they got it right.
至少我猜是真的
At least I'm guessing that's ture.
还有你  小伙子
And you, young man,
你不用再玩第一人称射击游戏了
instead of playing first-person shooters,
我们会给你一把真枪
we're going to put a real rifle in your hands.
接招  第二修正案
Take that, Second Amendment!
第二修正案保障个人拥有枪支的权利
该开始治疗了  马姬
It's time to start healing, Marge.
我喜欢你的口音
I love your accent.
我都不知道我有口音
I didn't know I had one.
这是我们唯一的电脑
This is our one computer,
你可以用它跟你过去的网络生活
on which you can say 'Auf Wiedersehen' forever
永远地道个别
to your old online life.
再见了  照片墙
Farewell, Instagram,
脸书  邻里
Facebook, and NextDoor.
你们都让我开心过  也担惊受怕过
You all entertained me and scared me.
没错  马姬  就是这样
Yes, Marge, yes.
把那些让你像匹诺曹一样疯狂起舞的
Cut forever the puppet strings that have made you
木偶线统统剪断
dance like a psychotic Pinocchio.
删除我的账号
无法删除脸书账号
Facebook accounts cannot be deleted.
请勿尝试  请勿尝试
Do not try. Do not try.
怎么了  侯默
What is wrong, Homer?
怎么愁眉苦脸的
Why the pickle puss?
我不知道没有在线纸牌  我要怎么过下去
I don't know if I can live in a world without online solitaire.
我有办法
I have an answer for you.
还没拆封
It's sealed.
我来拆封
I will open the plastic.
盒子也没拆
The box is shut.
我来打开
I will open the box.
-你能不能  -我来发牌
- Could you... - I-I will deal the cards.
你能不能再
And also...
我来玩纸牌
I will play the solitaire!
我还差张A
I need a jack.
我干什么都要用到手机
I used my phone for everything.
除了打电话给送我手机的爸妈
Except to call the parents who gave it to me.
你现在就能打电话给他们
You call them now.
你好  爸爸
Hello, Dad.
你别说话
You don't say.
他怎么说
What did he say?
他恨我
He hates me.
好吧  我们就随便聊聊  什么都行
Okay, okay. Let's just talk. Any subject.
除了电子游戏
Except video games.
一滴眼泪顺着我的脸颊滑下
A tear rolled down my face,
同时我的角色踩着她的尸体跳了一段鬼步舞
as my avatar did the electric shuffle on her corpse.
-真棒  -这游戏太赞了
- Yes! - That game is awesome!
局面已经失控了
I'm losing control.
但问题不大
But that's all right.
如今的治疗师有着多种高效的治疗手段
Today's therapists have many effective options.
毒气说明你又搞砸了
The gas is never a good sign.
不得不说
I have to say,
这些脱离电子产品的劝说
all this talk about no devices
让我更加想念我的手机了
has really made me want my phone.
是啊  今天我和别人谈论天气时
I know, I was talking with some guys about the weather,
突然发现
and I realized,
我根本不知道库比蒂诺今天的气温
I have no idea what the temperature is in Cupertino.
我需要手机
I need my phone.
我也是  万一小丑阿壳发微博了怎么办
Me, too. What if Krusty posted a tweet?!
我必须转发
I must retweet!
我需要手机
I need my phone!
我必须转发
-我需要手机  -我必须转发
- I need my phone! - I must retweet!
-我必须转发  -我需要手机
- I must retweet! - I need my phone!
我们不能走
We can't leave!
专家说电子产品比海洛因更难戒掉
Studies show tech is more addictive than heroin.
百度和抖音上已经辟谣了
Google and TikTok say that's a lie.
我们需要治疗
We have to be cured.
你简直错得离谱  马姬
You couldn't be more wrong, Marge.
简直离谱
You couldn't be more wrong.
自从我国建国以来
Since this nation was founded,
每个家庭都存在着无法回避的难题
families have faced the problem of
如何每天待在一起还能不被对方烦死
staying together without driving each other crazy.
在最初的两百年里
For the first 200 years,
人们在家拉小提琴  后来爆发了内战
they played fiddle music until they had a war.
从此某优秀的体制消亡了
It was a good system.
后来人们开始围在火炉旁收听电台
Then, they came up with sitting around a radio.
但由于没有屏幕
But without a screen,
还得时不时地看见家人的脸
they still had time to look at each other..
所以爆发了...二战
So... World War II.
直到发明了电视
With peace came TV,
给硅谷精英们争取了时间来发明出
which bought Silicon Valley the time to invent the devices
可以让我们完全孤立的电子产品
that isolate us completely.
也正因为如此  美国人民
Finally, the American family was safe...
终于安全了
from itself.
你说的有一句是真的吗
Is any of that true?
一旦我发到知乎上
Once I post it on Reddit,
就是真的了
it will be.
隆德医生
好了  进去说声再见  然后拿了东西就走
Okay, we'll just say goodbye and then we'll get our things.
这里什么情况
What's going on here?
我还以为这里不许用电子产品
I thought this was a screen-free environment.
病人们是不允许的
It is, for the patients.
但我们工作人员还有非法副业要忙
But the rest of us have side hustles to perpetrate.
"在家隔离也能日赚400元
"I'm making $400 a day from home.
快点击链接了解一下"
Want to know how?"
你在用我的账号发垃圾邮件吗
You're sending that spam through my e-mail account?
我们入住的时候你盗取了她的密码
You stole her password when she checked in!
和其他康复中心不一样  你这是黑店
Unlike every other rehab, this one is a scam!
我们要揭发你丑恶的罪行
And we're gonna expose you to the world!
恐怕不行
I'm afraid not.
你们签了合同
You signed a contract.
而且每个出口都配有激光侦测系统
And every exit is guarded by a laser-detection system.
你建康复中心还配激光系统的吗
You have lasers at a rehab center?
我再提醒你们一句
Let me remind you,
这是一家黑店
this is an evil rehab center.
寂静之地
公园
危险
注意
已被隐形激光覆盖
用婴儿爽身粉
小屁屁痒痒了吗
安全了
好宝宝
聪明宝宝
鱼
香蕉
邮局罢工
鲍勃·西格
美国著名摇滚歌手
云母  很  便宜
木星一号
有人叫了木星一号吗
Anyone order a ride from Jupiter One?
我要坐宇宙飞船回家啦
Ooh, I'm riding in a spaceship.
把这个骗子扔进我们
Stick that spammer in the darkest,
最黑暗最潮湿的牢房里  阿卢
dankest cell we've got, Lou.
离无线路由器最远的那间
The one furthest from the Wi-Fi.
只有一格信号  人渣
One bar, scumbag.
一格信号足够我扰乱你的网易云日推了
One bar is all I need to scramble your Spotify suggestions.
希望你们喜欢小河流乐队
Hope you like Little River Band.
上世纪70年代澳大利亚著名乐队
《追忆往事》-小河流乐队
Reminiscing - Little River Band
快别放了  求求你把警笛打开
No, no! Please, turn the siren on.
舒服多了
Much better.
十二个甜甜圈分给三个警察
Only 12 doughnuts for three cops...
反正也没法平均分配
well, there's no way to divide them evenly,
我就全吃掉好了
so, uh, I'll just eat them all.
韦根队长  我可以治疗你的食物成瘾
Captain Wiggum, I could help you with your food addiction.
你在说什么
Uh, what do you mean?
从心理学角度讲  你就像是带着枪的婴儿
Psychologically, you are a baby with a gun,
不停地往嘴里塞食物
sticking food in his mouth.
干啥啥不行  吃饭第一名
Eat, eat, eat, all the day, like a schwein.
你当侧写师正合适
Wow, you are such a great profiler.
有了你  我们就不需要DNA取证了
With you, we wouldn't even need DNA evidence.
我已经受够了采集罪犯的精液样本
So sick of getting criminals to give semen samples.
队长  用不着精液
Uh, Chief, you don't need semen.
一撮头发就可以了
A lock of hair will do.
啥玩意
It what?!